你得想想办法 我弟弟是无辜的
You got do something,my brother is innocent.
他可是美国公民啊
He's an American citizen.
对此我也无能为力
Look,there's nothing I can do about that.
你当然能
Of course there is
再去犯罪现场看看 定能证实清白
back at the crime scene,that'll prove
你看 我不过是个夜间办事员而已
Look,I'm a night clerk,okay?
你若真想解决问题
If you want someone who can really do something,
最好等领事来
you're gonna have to wait for the consul
他早上才上班
he gets in in the morning.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
那我自己来搞定
That ain't gonna cut it.
你兄弟
Your brother,
关在哪个监狱?
where do they have him incarcerated?
索纳监狱
Sona.
怎么了?
What?
那里关的都是最穷凶极恶的罪犯
The worst of the worst are there,
别的监狱都不收
men no other prison will take.
一年前 他们野蛮暴动过
They rioted so badly a year ago,
守卫都撤了出来
the guards pulled out,
留下他们自生自灭
just left them to themselves.
成千上万的小偷 强奸犯 杀人犯
A thousand thieves,rapists,murderers.
政府干脆退避三舍
The government just stays back,
保持他们的原样
keeps the perimeter.
都说那是"单行道"
To them,Sona's a one-way street.
只有进
What goes in
没有出
never comes out
除非死了
unless it's dead.
YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
最新最快的影视字幕请登录：www.YYeTs.net
■
字幕：YYeTs人人影视字幕组  后期：梁良
此人未证实有罪
Somebody didn't do their due diligence on this guy,
我们要求将他转移至更
and we need him moved to a facility that's a little
适合的机构
more moderate.
行吗?
All right?
谢谢你
Thank you.
是这样的 好消息是
All right,the good news is as of yesterday
从昨天起 你重获自由了
you're a free man.
你无需再担心什么了
You got nothing to worry about.
我担心我弟弟
Just my brother.
好吧 你们俩的事迹传得很神
Right. Well,that's a heck of a story,you two.
消息甚至传到了这
That made the news even down here.
我听说你还有个儿子
And I understand you have a son as well?
-没错 -叫LJ 小林肯?
-Yeah. Uh-huh. -LJ Lincoln Jr.?
他得知你恢复清白身 一定很兴奋
He must be ecstatic about your exoneration.
还没联系上他
Still trying to reach him.
你可以告诉我们他在哪里
Well,hey,tell us where he is.
-我们派人去 -我自己能搞定
-We'll send -Let me handle that.
让我们还是先关注迈克吧
Let's just focus on Michael.
好的 好消息是
Okay,well,good news is is that much
你所说的一切与犯罪现场吻合
of what you're saying is checking out at the crime scene.
被害人的确有一把特工专用左轮手枪
The victim did have a service revolver
上面刻有政府编号
with U.S. government numbers on it.
凶器既然已经发现
And if a weapon was found,then that lends
那么对自卫一说提供了有利物证
real credence to self-defense as a motive.
很好
Great.
他们有没有发现别的?
They,uh,find anything else?
-比如说哪方面? -包
-Like what? -A bag.
里面有什么?
What was in it?
有些钱吧
A little money.
没有发现 不好意思
No,sorry.
没关系
Of course they didn't.
不管发生什么情况
Yeah,well,whatever the case,
对于你兄弟而言
regarding your brother,I have managed
我都会设法做些改变
to make a little headway.
我已作出了安排
I arranged for a transfer
把你兄弟转移到别的地方
for your brother to another facility,
明天就能生效
effective tomorrow.
那里要安全
It's a lot safer,
-干净得多 -很好
-it's a lot cleaner. -Great.
如我所想那样 会有足够的证据
And if this is stacking up like I think it is,
我有十足的把握 所有控告都会撤销
I'd be pretty confident the charges will be dropped.
他会无罪释放?
He'd be free?
可能还要面对美国方面的指控
Well,he'd still face charges in the U.S.
但那是出狱以后的事了?
But out of there?
没错
Yes.
这里有 有集体食堂吗?
Is there is there a mess hall here?
集体食堂?
Mess hall?
还要点水
And some water.
求求你 我快渴死了
I'm dying of thirst. Please.
求求你了
Please.
这里倒是有些水
There's some water.
去死吧
Bite me.
你说什么?
What'd you say?
我什么也没说
I didn't say nothing.
喝了它
Drink it.
听见没有
You hear me?
喝了它
Drink
伙计 这里就是这样的
Hey,get used to it,man.
我也好几天没吃东西了
I haven't eaten for days.
起来
Come on.
你还好吧?
How are you doing?
阿历克斯 你想怎样?
What do you want,Alex?
你太聪敏了 居然想出在船上放毒品栽赃
You're so clever like planting the drugs on the boat.
这太嘲讽了
That's a big irony.
关在监狱里的罗曼
Lawman in jail.
你现在罪有应得了
You are exactly where you belong.
不 这就是你错误的地方
No,that's where you're wrong.
我需要你的帮助
And that's where you're gonna help me.
这几天我就要接受庭审了
I will have a court date one of these days,
你到时也会出庭
and you will be there on the stand.
你会告诉大家事实你计划了这一切
And you will tell the truth that you planted this
你设计栽赃 我就可以回家了
and you set this up,and I'm gonna go home.
这太嘲讽了 我对天发誓是你设的局
That's funny,I could have sworn you set this up.
我设的局? 我被关在这儿
I set this up? I'm in here.
幕后者到底对我有何企图?
What does the Company want with me?
为什么挑选巴拿马?
Why Panama?
你觉得我这样子像知道这一切吗?
What,you think I know what they wanted?
我受他们控制
They had me.
听命于他们
I did what they asked me to do
在巴拿马逮捕你
arrest you in Panama
并移送回来
hand you over.
这 这一切
That's it. That's,that's
这一切现在听来都是旧事了
That's old news,huh?
从今天开始 我们重新回归正途
This is the first day of the rest of our lives.
不如我们联手 怎样?
How about we work together,you know?
互相帮助 一起逃出去
Help each other out.
但我每次看到你
Except every time I look at you,
就想起那个杀了我父亲的凶手
all I can see is the man who killed my father.
你自谋生路吧
You're on your own.
把我老公带出来
My husband Bring him out
我知道他昨天被杀了
I know he was killed last night
有人给我打电话了
Someone called
把我老公带出来
Bring my husbang out now
小心点
Be careful.
在这里登记 进去后
Sign here to say that once inside,
根据我国法律 就你自己负责了
you're on your own by the law,
任何意外都不受军方或者法律保护
that you're not protected by the military in case of an assault.
任何协助在押犯逃跑的企图
And any attempt to assist an inmate trying to escape
都以死罪论处
will be met with a lethal response.
想都没有想过
Wouldn't dream of it.
怎样
So
不怎样
感觉我站错边了
Feel like I'm on the wrong side.
你在你该在的地方
You're on the right side.
可你不在
You're not.
要帮我越狱?
Gonna break me out?
一路亡命太辛苦了
Too tiring. All that running.
或许你已经把逃亡靴给丢了
Yeah,well,maybe you should have lost the cowboy boots.
你害怕了?
You scared?
-我现在就要把你救出来 -林肯
-I'm getting you out of here,man. -Linc.
听着 上头准备把你转移到安全的地方
Listen,the Consulate's arranged to transfer you to a
大约一个月后 你就有重获自由的机会
safer facility until the trial which is about a month.
他们说你有很大机会无罪释放
They say you got a good shot of walking out of here a free man.
什么时候转移?
When's the transfer?
明天
Tomorrow.
再等等 多等一天
Just just hold on,man,one more day.
希望你能快点找到她的消息
You know,I keep waiting for you to mention a certain someone.
兄弟 我不知道她在哪
I don't know where she is,man.
你得找到她
Well,you got to find her.
我会的
I will.
林肯 这对我很重要
She's important to me,Linc.
要是莎拉发生了什么事
If anything happens to Sara
一切都会好的 兄弟
It's going to be fine,man.
我保证
I promise.
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
好吗?
All right?
你是美国人 对吧?
American,right?
我热爱美国
I love America.
NBA 特雷西·麦迪的神奇表现
NBA. Tracy McGrady shooting the ball in the hoop from downtown.
不管你想推销什么 我都不感兴趣
Whatever you're selling,I'm not buying.
推销?
Selling?
我只是想跟你说说篮球
I just want to talk basketball.
你喜欢哪个球队?
Who's your team?
小子 跟我们走
Let's go,blanco.
带你熟悉下环境
Orientation.
我没兴趣
I'm not interested.
没你选的份
It's not for you to decide.
守卫说我得在15分钟后离开
Guards say I have to be out in 15 minutes.
把他们带进来
Bring them in.
我真希望他们没让你们吃什么苦头
Well,I hope they haven't been treating you too poorly.
如果有的话 我应该有所耳闻了
I should hear of it if you have.
我想你们能看出这地方与众不同
I think as you can tell,Sona is unlike any other place in the world.
那帮守卫去年仓皇而逃
Huh? Since the riots of last year,they left us here to rot.
他们认为我们会内耗而亡
They figured we would just destroy ourselves,
恰恰相反 我们队伍更壮大了
but instead,we've thrived.
借助于巴拿马运河
With the canal,Panama is now
巴拿马现在成了全球罪犯的孵化基地
a breeding ground for international crime.
我们这的人来自27个不同国家
27 different nationalities we have here.
但不是一个帮派的
But not one gang.
没有一起种族歧视案例
Not one racially-motivated incident.
这都归功于我
It's just me.
平等主义
Egalitarianism
这是我的信仰
I believe is the word.
你不同意吗?
Huh? Did I get that right?
你说是就是了
Right as rain.
操练一下果然长进了
That's what practice does for you.
你们有什么要向我汇报的吗?
Now,is there anything you want to tell me?
我想知道你们被关进来的原因
Any history that you bring to this place that I should know about?
我想你没说实话
I don't think you're quite telling me the truth,
斯科菲尔德先生
Mr. Scofield.
我们已经听到了风声 老兄
We get the news,man.
你在CNN上俨然是个超级明星了
You were quite the superstar on CNN.
救出了你哥后
Man breaks brother out
然后逃亡到巴拿马
and flees to Panama.
但在这你可行不通了
But you're not a superstar here
你没意识到这点吗?
You realize that,don't you?
我不想在起什么波澜
I'm not going to make waves.
凭你的能耐也办不到
It wouldn't be within your power.
我也听说过你们俩
I heard about the two of you.
你们今天闯祸了
You two in the hall today.
但你俩如果想解决问题的话
Now,if you would like to sort your problems out,
方法很简单
it's very simple here.
两人之间意见不同
A man has a beef with another,he makes his problem known.
就直接用男人的方式解决问题
And then we deal with it directly
就在那里
as men over there.
没那个必要
Won't be necessary.
你一直那样发抖的吗
You always shake like that?
还是仅仅出于对某人的畏惧
Or just when you're scared of someone?
你呢?
What about you?
老大 不要伤害我
Dont hurt me man.
我不想惹什么麻烦
I dont want any trouble.
蠢货 绝不允许
Asshole Never
永远别在我的地盘随地大小便
Never use my floor as a bathroom
我想他明白了
I think he gets the message.
我们两个可以单挑
We could go you and me
就在这里
right here.
你真有胆识
You're a brave man,huh?
有种
Brave man.
你很幸运 我现在温和多了
You're lucky I've been meditating.
换作以前 早一枪毙了你
Before,I couldn't take my finger off the trigger,but now
但我现在懂得了控制情绪
now I have mind control.
完全的控制
Complete control.
思想
Mind
身体
body
还有灵魂
and soul.
滚出去吧
Get out
快滚
浪费我们的时间
He's a waste of our time.
谁能想象索纳出了这样的风云人物
Who would have thought a famous person in Sona.
弱者总是延续弱势
Weak people rally around fame.
他们祈祷上苍 他们对此深信不疑
They worship it. They're blinded by it.
正如你所知
And as you can tell,there are many people
这里还有很多弱者
of weak character behind these walls.
没错 他们会跟随像这样的人
Yes,they will follow a man like this,
他们会给他立碑纪念
and they will put him on a pedestal.
他很有魅力 是吗 宝贝?
He has that charisma,right,mami?
他可比不上你
He's no you.
宝贝 你不用来迎合我
Ah,you don't have to pander me,mami.
我可不是三岁小孩
Soy un hombre maduro.
他很帅 不是吗?
He's good looking,right?
没错 他是很帅
Si. He is good looking.
他是这里最帅的 不是吗?
He's the best looking man in the prison,right?
和你不能比
Not compared to you.
宝贝 让我来告诉你
Let me tell you, mammi.
谁知道呢
Who knows
或许是吧
Maybe
臭婊子 给我滚蛋
Pack up, whore.
别让我再看到你
You are gone.
莎拉
Sara
莎拉 唐克瑞蒂是个美国人
Sara Tancredi she's an American.
她失踪了
She's missing.
我们没有她的任何消息
We don't have a report of anything like that.
但如果有的话 给我电话 号码在背面
But if you do,you call me;the number's on the back.
好的 先生
Okay,ser.
有任何消息就打给我 好吗?
Anything,you call me,all right?
会的
Will do.
谢谢
Thank you.
你哪弄来的鞋子?
Where'd you get shoes?
该干活还钱付租金了
It's time to start earning your rent around here.
这里不用租金的
There's no rent here.
-这是监狱 -继续说啊
It's prison.Keep talking.
要上去了
It's going up.
给
Here.
干活时间到了
Work time's started right now.
哪?
Where?
哦 不
Uh-uh. Hell no.
绝对没门
Absolutely not.
再敢放屁
One more word from you,
我让你吃屎 明白没?
and I will drown you in here,you understand?
快点 干活
Now,work.
做完后拿去下水道烧掉
Burn it down in the sewers when you're done.
有新人来了
一个美国人
还有别的事么?
他有只假手
斯科菲尔德 有人来看你了
Scofield,una visita
Scofield,visita
斯科菲尔德 先生
Ah,Mr. Scofield.
埃利奥特 派克
Elliot Pike.
找我什么事
What do you want?
说实话 是来代表你的
Well,to be frank,to represent you.
-你是律师? -算是吧
You're a lawyer? Of sorts.
法院已经指派了律师给我
The court already appointed me a lawyer.
那或许我可以用别的方法帮你
Then perhaps I can be of assistance in a different way.
我有点怀疑
Somehow I doubt that.
我的靠山可厉害者呢 斯科菲尔德先生
I got a lot of big guns behind me,Mr. Scofield,
你或许会需要他们的
people you might like to have in your corner
你是否该考虑下 越狱呢
should you ever decide,say to break out of here.
你是谁?
Who are you?
我们可以从各方面帮助你
We can assist you in every possible way
一旦你能越过那道墙
once you get past that wall.
像你这样一个身怀绝技的人
There's a reason a guy like you,
被关到这是有原因的 知道么
with your skill set,was put in here,you know.
谈话到此为止
This conversation's over.
斯科菲尔德 你得听听我说的
You ought to hear what I have to say,Scofield.
我们想让事情简单点
We're trying to do this the easy way.
你他妈搞什么 敢动我东西?
What the hell are you doing taking my stash?
说啊 小娘们
Cough it up,you little bitch.
-我没拿 -东西在哪?
I didn't do it. Where is it?
-在哪? -不是我
Where is it? It wasn't me.
你懂私自斗殴的规矩吧
You know the rules about extra-curricular fights
这里可行不通
It doesn't happen here.
他拿走了属于我的东西
He took something that belongs to me.
他不大正常
He's out of his mind.
这事很容易弄明白
Well,it seems pretty easy to get to the bottom of this
搜他的身
check him.
检查他的地方
Check his area.
真见鬼
That's bull.
你们都是
You're both
贱人
scumbags.
伙计 你和我
You and me,man.
我们还没完呢
We're not done here.
你见过这个女的没有
You haven't seen her?
有长得相似的入住过吗
No one like this has checked in?
先生 抱歉没有见过
No Sir.
你真的确定吗
You're absolutely sure?
谢谢
Thanks.
是我
Yeah.
布鲁斯先生 我是伊萨斯队长
Mr. Burrows. Captain Itzuris
正在治安官的办公室里
at the constable's office.
我们找到了一个美国女人
We found an American woman
符合你对你朋友唐克瑞蒂小姐的描述
matching the description of your friend,Ms. Tancredi.
在哪
Where?
停尸房
At the morgue.
他说的什么
What's he saying?
我们不能吃这些
That we can't eat.
那我们应该吃什么
What are we supposed to eat?
求你了 来这一周 我都没进过食
Please. I haven't eaten in the week since i have been here..
他们想要我们像狗一样的讨食
They expect us to forage,like dogs.
我会死的 怎么都是死
I'll die.I will literally die.
伙计 那就死好了
Hang in there,man.
自娱自乐吧 帅哥
Playing by yourself.Same old Pretty.
就是不大合群啊 对吧
Just not good at making friends,are you?
我们之间没什么好说的
We got nothing to say to each other.
换个角度来说
On another note,
如果这是一部由政府导演的大片
on a big picture note,them big government types
把我陷害得这么惨
that shook me down so hard,
为什么他们要把你搞到这里来
why is it they wanted you here?
索纳监狱就是他们的兴趣所在?
Was it Sona they was interested in?
我就是这么想的
That's what I'm thinking.
想让我到这个烂乡下地方来把你搅晕
Want me to get you down here,up in this very county.
你是怎么认为的?
What do you think it is,huh?
你认为真有人会对索纳监狱有兴趣?
You think it's Sona?
谁会对这种破烂地方有兴趣?
Who'd be interested in a dump like this?
有人逃跑
Runner Runner
不 不
No No
谢谢您通知我
Thanks for getting back to me.
不用谢
No problem.
尸体今天上午被钓出池塘
The body was fished out of the pond
-今早发现的第一件 -在哪里发现的?
-first thing this morning. -Where?
卡雷 瑟森塔赛思
Calle Sesenta-Seis.
就在阿凡尼达 科隆西边
Just west of Avenida Colon.
先生?
Sir?
那是我最后一次看见她的地方
That's the last place I saw her.
这不是她
It's not her.
有人控告你
Someone's thrown the glove down on you.
还是很严重的事情呢 是吧?
The gauntlet,right?
是啊 只是我们都知道我没拿那些药
Yeah,except we both know I didn't take those drugs.
我不是法官
I'm not the judge.
我不处理这里的上诉
I don't deal in the claims people make.
我只确保这里得按照规则运作
I just make sure the rules are followed.
规则说一切冤屈的处理方法
And the rules say all grievances are dealt with
都是2个人到圈里决斗
two men in a ring,a fight.
我明天就离开了 没有必要这样
I'll be leaving tomorrow,so that won't be necessary.
也许对你来说没有必要
It may not be necessary to you,
但是对我来说很必要
but it is to me.
我有职责维护这里的秩序
I have a duty to maintain order here
用一个铁定的合法体制来确保
an ironclad legal system that assures that
没人能自作主张处理他们的矛盾
no one goes independent with their grievances,
那可是其他监狱里常有的事
as is so often the case in other prisons.
在这里
Here,
存在着一个体制
there is a system,
这个体制就代表了秩序
and that system means order.
所以不管你是否赞同
So whether you agree with it or not
都和我没有关系
does not matter to me.
我的议程比你的更重要
There's a larger agenda than yours.
如果我拒绝会怎么样?
What happens if I refuse?
我们会去找你
We'll come for you.
我能保证你会得到一个
And I can guarantee you that is an outcome
你不喜欢的结局
that you will not like.
告诉我
Tell me something
你总是用计来使人决斗吗?
do you always set up your fights?
我和那一点关系都没有
I had nothing to do with it.
整个监狱和我有冲突的人
And yet the only one in this whole prison
至今只有你
who has a problem with me is you.
我会很乐意见到巨星陨落
I'd be glad to see you go down superstar
继续 继续做
Go on,keep going.
在角落里把它烧了
You burn it around the corner.
伙计
Buddy.
可以帮我一个忙吗
Think you can do me a favor?
休想
Bite me.
我能给你吃的
I can feed you.
几周前 我和你一样的处境
A few weeks ago,I was in your shoes.
好几天没有东西吃
Didn't get any food for days.
他们想让我死
They'd have let me die,
就像他们想让你死一样
just like they're gonna let you die.
回到给我吃的那个话题
Get back to the"feed me"part.
鸡肉
Chicken.
伙计 你哪里来的鸡肉
Man,where'd you get chicken?
那不是鸡肉
That's not chicken.
-还要再来点吗 -要
-Want some more? -Yeah.
那你要帮我跑个腿
Then you're gonna have to run an errand for me.
跑什么腿
What kind of errand?
-爸爸 是我 -LJ
-Dad? It's me. -LJ.
你在哪里
Where are you?
我在巴拿马
I'm in Panama.
什么
What?
你
How
你怎么得到这个号码的
How'd you get this number?
我碰到莎拉
Well,I ran into Sara.
她从领事馆得到你的号码
She got your number from the consulate.
爸爸 我得挂了
Dad,I'm cutting out.
LJ 我听不清楚
LJ,I can't hear you,man.
爸爸 照我说的做
Dad,do this.
和我们在加菲 普莱斯大厦见面
Meet us at the restaurant in the Garfield Price building
在顶楼的餐馆
at the top.
加菲什么
Garfield what?
8点半
8:30
决斗时间
Time to fight,blanco
希望你没事
Best to make your peace with God.
都安排好了?
all right?
当然
Come on
10对1
Ten to one.
没人喜欢那美国佬
No one wants the American.
什么?居然要10对1
What? Even at 10-1?
所以他必须要投靠我们
There's a reason he chose World.
已经连续死了6个了
Six consecutive life terms,okay?
擦干净
Clean it up.
我只是开个玩笑
I'm just kidding,man.
放心吧
Tranquilo
当然啦 因为您
Surely,it's beneath a man of your status
在这正是把握全局
to be walking around like that
的核心人物
all sticky-like.
放了他
Leave him.
你什么意思
What do you propose?
帮您擦鞋
Ablution.
为了投靠您的门下
A humble sign of friendship from a stranger
以表达我最诚挚的善意
who's come into your house.
哦 对不起
Sorry about that.
我只是个废人
Just half a man down here.
你叫什么?
What's your name,
就叫我"朋友"好了
You can just call me"friend."
对着膝关节就是一脚
Go for the kneecap.
恩 就是你想的那样
You,uh you hit it
直接踹上去 膝关节就断了
straight on,it'll buckle,
你就能把那家伙彻底放倒
and you'll take the guy out of commission.
使用诡计 这就是你的伎俩?
Fighting dirty? That's your secret?
这世界上没什么光明正大的事
I didn't think there was any such thing as clean
尤其是在这
in a place like this.
阿历克斯 我很意外
You know,I'm surprised,Alex.
没想到你还会关心人
It almost sounds like you care.
你可是我离开这鬼地方的关键
You're my get-out-of-jail-free card.
要活着
Just survive.
记得踹膝盖 要用尽力气
Kneecap,really hard.
祝你好运
Good luck,man.
上帝保佑你
God bless,man.
两只狗之间有争执
We got a disagreement between two dogs
一个是瘾君子 另一个是扒手
a drug addict and a thief.
两个我都不能饶恕
And I condone neither.
我已经金盘洗手了
And I wash my hands of both of them.
但是我们是有规矩的
But they have an issue,and we have rules.
没有规矩 我们就和野蛮没两样
And without rules,we're nothing but savages.
所以 我们要尊重规矩
Therefore,with proper respect for the rules,
这次的决斗只有一个规定
this fight is engaged with only one rule
不能用武器
no weapons.
单挑
Only man versus man,
不能借助物品和障碍
without augmentation or handicap.
要说的都说完了
I'm done talking.
我不会打的
I'm not going to fight
你还没明白规矩 朋友
I don't think you understand the rules,friend.
只有活着的人才能走出去
Only one man comes out alive.
不能用武器 规矩不能坏 记得吗?
Rules are rules. Remember?
如果我们没规矩
If we don't have them
我们就是野蛮人
we're savages.
对不起
Oh,excuse me.
你没有穿外套
You have no jacket.
我只是过来等下人 通融一下
Come on,man. I'm just meeting someone. Give me a break.
这是个高级场所
Well,this is a nice place.
要求要穿外套
It requires jackets.
我没有
Well,I don't
外套
have a jacket.
必须要穿外套
It requires jackets.
好
Fine.
麻烦你
Excuse me.
你会讲英语吗?
You speak English?
那你认识美元的吧?
How about American?
请给我一杯水
Can I grab a water,please?
你大老远来巴拿马
Please tell me you didn't come
不是只为了喝杯水吧
all the way to Panama for the water.
为了家庭
Family.
夹克挺不错的 萨杰奥
That's a nice jacket,Sergio.
说来话长了
It's a long story.
谢谢
Thank you.
你在等人吧?
You're waiting for someone,huh?
嗯
Uh-huh.
我早该知道
I should have known.
长相不错的男人总是先被人挑走了
Good-looking ones are always taken.
你的脸怎么了?
What happened to your face?
猫抓的
A cat.
猫 一定是好大的猫
Cat. It's a big cat.
你不要提问题
You push anything too far into a corner,
太刨根问底了好吗
and the claws will come out.
夫人 也许你总是选择的时机不对
Your timing's all wrong,lady.
噢 得了吧 过来一起吧
Oh,come on. Hang out.
我很愿意 只不过现在不行
I'd like to but it ain't the right time.
林肯 的确时机不合适
Yes,it is,Lincoln.
看起来我们有得聊了
We have a lot to discuss.
特别是 关于你弟弟
Specifically,your brother.
我强烈建议
I highly suggest
你跟他聊聊
you talk to him.
把里面的死尸带出来吧
The dead men inside Bring them out
我想葬了他
I want to bury him
他们会被葬在这
They will be buried here.
除非他们家人出面 自己料理后事
Unless their family members step forward to make their own arrangements.
转运我去另一个监狱的事情进行得怎么样?
How are we coming with the transfer?
有一伙人
There are some people
希望你可以帮他们把里面的某个人弄出去
that want you ask someone out of there.
我知道
Yeah,I know.
他们有跟我接触过
Some guy already approached me.
我拒绝了他们
I said,"No,thank you."
你必须待在里面
You got to stay.
你说什么?
What are you talking about?
那个人的名字是詹姆斯 韦斯勒
His name's James Whistler
不行 不行 林肯 我不想再这么做了
No,no,no,no,Linc,I can't do that again.
迈克
Michael.
说话
Talk.
爸爸
Dad.
爸爸 对不起
Dad,I'm so sorry.
他们抓住了我和莎拉
They got me and Sara.
照他们的吩咐去做好吗
Please,do what they want.
爸爸 求你了
Dad,please.
你有一周的时间
You got a week
找到那个韦斯勒
to find this Whistler guy.
然后想办法把他弄出来
Get him out of there.
否则 他们
Otherwise,they,uh
莎拉和LJ 他们就死定了
Sara and LJ they both die.